In the previous videos,
在之前的视频中
we used many transformers and estimators.
我们使用了许多转换器和评估器
Just to recall, a transformer implements
回想一下 转换器使用
a method transform that turns a data frame into another URL.
Transfrom 的方法将一个 dataframe 转换为另一个 dataframe
We use a transformer method to organize text,
我们先使用 transform 方法 然后对文本分词
scale some columns, and assemble reactors.
对一些列的数据进行了缩放 然后把多列数据合并为一个向量
An estimator on the other hand pits or trains on data.
评估器对数据进行拟合或训练
It implements methods fit, which accepts a data frame
它通过 fit方法 输入一个 dataframe
and produces a mole which is a transformer.
然后产出一个模型 也就是一个 转换器
So for example, if we check the type of model
例如 如果我们看一下之前
that we trained in the previous video,
视频里训练过的模型的类型
we can see that it's a logistic regression model.
可以看到它是一个逻辑回归模型
So it is a transformer.
这是一个转换器
If we check the type of layer two,
如果我们检查 lr2 的类型
you will see that it is logistic regression,
你会看到它是逻辑回归
but it doesn't really say that it is an estimator.
但它并没有说这是一个评估器
Let's build an actual pipeline.
接下来我们将构建一个管道
So in Spark, similarly to other frameworks,
在 Spark 中 与其他框架类似
for example circuit-learn, we can chain
例如 scikit-learn ，我们可以把
transformers and estimators
转换器和评估器连接在一起
after one another to build a whole pipeline.
建立一个完整的管道
In Spark, the only restriction is that these steps
在Spark中 唯一的限制是这些步骤
need to form a directed acyclic graph.
需要形成有向无环图
If you recall what that means is that
如果你还记得这个知识点 它指的是
there isn't any cycle in these dependencies.
这个依赖关系中没有任何循环
So as we go from stage to stage,
所以当我们一步一步搭建管道时
we should not get back to the point where we started out.
我们不可以回到我们开始的地方
So let just recreate our logistic regression model,
那么让我们重新创建逻辑回归模型
but by building a pipeline.
但是这次是建立一条管道
I will create a new clean data frame
我将创建一个新的 dataframe
just by importing the same data set we have been using.
导入我们一直使用的数据集
So we have our data frame with the columns.
所以我们 dataframe 已经好了
We are already familiar with.
里面的列我们也很熟悉了
Now, we need to define all the stages
现在，我们需要定义这个计划的
that we go into this plan. All right.
所有阶段好了
So we will need a RegexTokenizer
我们需要一个 RegexTokenizer
that turns the body into a list of words.
将问题内容变成一个单词列表
Then we will have a CountVectorizer,
然后我们创建一个CountVectorizer
they will transform the words into term frequencies.
它会将单词转换为单词出现的频率
For this example, I chose a bigger
在这个例子中 我统计了更多单词
vocabulary size with 10,000 words.
一共 10,000 字
Then we have our IDF that turns
然后我们用 IDF 把
term frequencies into TF-IDF,
单词频率转换为 TF-IDF
and the output column of that will be called features,
并将其输出列称为特征列
so we can spare step.
这样我们可以节省一步
So with changing regexTokenizers CV and IDF together,
把 regexTokenizers CV 和 IDF  连接在一起后
we can create the features.
我们就可以创建特征了
We will also need to transform the string tags into numeric values,
我们还需要将字符串标签转换为数值
and we will call that column label.
我们将这列叫做 label
Afterwards, we can define our logistic regression model.
然后 我们可以定义逻辑回归模型了
We will use the same parameters as we used earlier.
我们将使用和之前相同的参数
Then the last step is to define the actual pipeline object.
然后最后一步是定义一个管道对象
In case steps are dependent on each other,
为防止步骤相互依赖
we will need to maintain their order.
我们需要维持他们的顺序
So for example, here we need to start with the regexTokenizer,
例如 这里我们需要从 regexTokenizer 开始
and then the countVectorizer,
然后是 countVectorizer
and then finally we can end the idea.
最后我们再加上 idf
Since the stringIndexer returns a string labels of numeric values,
由于 stringIndexer 是把文本转换为数值
it's independent from these previous steps.
它与之前的这些步骤无关
So we could have put the indexer in the very beginning,
我们也可以把 indexer 放在最开头
but I chose to put it after these three steps,
但是我选择把它放在这三个步骤之后
and then we can finally include the model itself.
最后我们把模型本身放进去
Now that we have the pipeline,
既然我们的管道创建好了
we just need to end it. Our model is ready.
我们只需要拟合它了我们的模型已经好了
The recycle returns transformer that we can use
结果会返回一个转换器
to get the prediction on the data set.
用来对数据做预测
I just use the training data set to see
我先用训练数据来看看
what the link is going to be.
预测的标签是什么
So if you look at the first record,
看一下第一个记录
we can see that there are two new columns.
我们可以看到有两个新列
So we have this probability column
这个是概率列
as well as the prediction itself.
以及预测本身
So if we look back,
我们看一下上面
you can see that the probability of the third label,
你可以看到第三个标签的概率
the count starts at zero is actually pretty high.
计数从零开始 这个概率非常高了
It's about 85 percent.
大概是85％
So this became our predicted label.
所以这就是我们预测的标签
So let's just check how this model predicted the labels.
那么我们来看看这个模型预测效果如何
So here, I'm just filtering the rules and the label,
在这里 我用 filter  把
and the prediction are the same,
标签和预测标签相同的行给过滤出来
and then count the number of these rows.
然后计算这些行的数量
So out of our 100,000 rows,
在我们的 100,000 行中
more than half of it got the prediction right,
超过一半的预测是对的
but of course, this accuracy
但当然 这个准确率
is measured on the training set itself.
是在训练集上测量的
So it is expected to be a bit inflated.
所以效果会偏好
In the next section, maybe I'll take a look
在下一节中 我们会看看
at how the string addressed properly our models.
在如何正确衡量模型效果